anti-agingstore.com 2016-10-21

# Privacy Policy

Anti-agingstore , llc is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of our Website, located at www. Anti-agingstore , llc.com and our related services.

### 1\. User Consent

By submitting Personal Data through our Website or related services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. A Note About Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of 13.

### 3\. A Note to Users Outside of the United States

Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

### 4\. Types of Data We Collect

Anti-agingstore , llc collects Personal Data and Anonymous Data from you when you visit our Website and when you send us information or communications."Personal Data" means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. "Anonymous Data" means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below.

#### Personal Data You Provide to Us

We collect Personal Data from you, such as your first and last name, e-mail and mailing addresses, password, and various demographic items such as number of children, ages, gender when you sign up for a Anti-agingstore , llc Account (as defined in the Terms of Service) and make purchases on the Website. When you order Products (as defined in the Terms of Service) on our Website, we will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, billing information and shipping information. We also retain information on your behalf, such as your credit card information for future purchases and addresses you add to your address book. If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail (e.g., in response to an employment opportunity posted on our Website), we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply, and any information that you submit to us (e.g., a resume). When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information. When you post messages on the message boards of our Website, the information contained in your posting will be stored on our servers and other users will be able to see it. We may also collect Personal Data, such as demographic information or personal preferences, from you via other points in our Website that state that Personal Data is being collected.

#### Personal Data Collected via Technology.

To make our Website, Products, and related services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect Personal Data from you, including your operating system and version, browser type and version, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. We also use Cookies (as defined below) and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and which you viewed. Like most Internet services, we automatically gather this Personal Data and store it in log files each time you visit our Website or access your Anti-agingstore , llc Account on our network. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of our Website may not work properly.

#### Personal Data That We Collect from You About Others

. If you decide to invite others to the Website or create a Anti-agingstore , llc Account for a third party to join the Website, we will collect your and the third party's names, e-mail addresses, and/or phone number in order to send an e-mail or text message and follow up with the third party. You or the third party may contact us at [support@beautyclub.net](mailto:http://beautyclub.net/index.php/admin/cms_wysiwyg/directive/___directive/e3tjb25maWcgcGF0aD0idHJhbnNfZW1haWwvaWRlbnRfZ2VuZXJhbC9lbWFpbCJ9fQ,,/) to request the removal of this information from our database.

### 5\. Use of Your Data

#### General Use.

In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. Anti-agingstore , llc uses your Personal Data in the following ways: to facilitate the creation of and secure your Anti-agingstore , llc/ Account on our network; identify you as a user in our system; provide improved administration of our Website and Product sales; improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Website and Products; send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your Anti-agingstore , llc Account was created; send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests; to do demographic analysis on our membership base; to send promotional communications as described in Section 8.1 below; to provide you with electronic newsletters; and/or to make telephone calls to you, from time to time, as a part of secondary fraud protection or to solicit your feedback.

#### Creation of Anonymous Data.

We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Products and services and improve Website navigation. Anti-agingstore , llc reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties at its discretion.

### 6\. Disclosure of Your Personal Data

#### Affiliates / Acquisitions.

Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, "Affiliates"), we may in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Data with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires Anti-agingstore , llc or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Other Disclosures.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), Anti-agingstore , llc may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) investigate any violation of the law or this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service; (b) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Anti-agingstore , llc; or (c) protect or defend the rights or property or safety of Anti-agingstore , llc or users of the Products or related services.

### 7\. Third parties

#### Personal and/or Anonymous Data Collected by Third Parties

Our provision of a link to any other website or location, such as the websites of our Product suppliers or payment processing service providers, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. When you click on such a link, you will leave our Website and go to another site. During this process, another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites.

#### Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers.

Except as otherwise stated in this policy, we do not generally sell, trade, share, or rent the Personal Data collected from our services to other entities. However, we may share your Personal Data with third party service providers to provide you with the Products and related services that we offer you through our Website; to conduct quality assurance testing; to provide technical support; or to provide specific services, such as synchronization of your contacts with other software applications, in accordance with your instructions. These third party service providers are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by Anti-agingstore , llc. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Data with our contractors and other service providers for the sole purpose of providing services to you.

### 8\. Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Data

#### Choices

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Data. By signing up for a Anti-agingstore , llc Account, you opt-in to receiving free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of the Website or the purchase of the Products ("Promotional Communications"). We will periodically send you free Promotional Communications. When you receive Promotional Communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe procedure provided in the e-mail you receive, or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Once we have processed your request, we will not send you promotional emails with respect to products and/or services offered by us of which you had opted out unless you opt back in to receiving such communications. If you make a purchase or an attempted purchase on one of our Sites, you will be opted back in to our newsletters and promotional communications until you opt out or unsubscribe once again. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to Personal Data.

You may change any of your Personal Data in your Anti-agingstore , llc Account by logging into your Anti-agingstore , llc// Account page or by sending an e-mail to [support@beautyclub.net](mailto:%7B%7Bconfig%20path=). You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

### 9\. Security of Your Personal Data

Anti-agingstore , llc is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also require you to enter a password to access your Anti-agingstore , llc// Account password to unauthorized people. Despite these measures, you should know that Anti-agingstore , llc cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Data and mistakes may happen.

### 10\. Contact Information

Anti-agingstore , llc welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at [service@ Anti-agingstore , llc.com](mailto:http://beautyclub.net/index.php/admin/cms_wysiwyg/directive/___directive/e3tjb25maWcgcGF0aD0idHJhbnNfZW1haWwvaWRlbnRfZ2VuZXJhbC9lbWFpbCJ9fQ,,/) or contact us at the following address or phone number:

Attn: Copyright/Legal  
anti-agingstore,llc 5023 W 120TH #181 BROOMFIELD, CO 80020   
E-mail: support@beautyclub.net

If you believe that Anti-agingstore , llc has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact Anti-agingstore , llc// by e-mail at [ Anti-agingstore , llc](mailto:%7B%7Bconfig%20path=). We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation.

### 11\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, in accordance with the Terms of Service. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your Anti-agingstore , llc Account with us. Continued use of our Website or purchase of Products following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

This Privacy Policy was last revised **July 17, 2012.**

### Contact Us:

Anti-agingstore , llc  
anti-agingstore,llc 5023 W 120TH #181 BROOMFIELD, CO 80020   
+1 (866) 918-4725
